# **Angela Robinette**

## **Front End Developer**

Billings, MT

Email: <u>angela@dev-angela.com</u> Website: <u>https://dev-angela.com/</u>

\* HTML \* CSS \* JavaScript \* Accessibility \* Security

### **Profile:**

Software developer with over 10 years' experience in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Passionate about creating aesthetically pleasing and functional websites which enhance a user's experience while providing special attention to accessibility and security. Previous experience in software development, graphics, and mentorship roles.

#### **Skills:**

HTML5	CSS3	JavaScript	PaintShop Pro	Figma
Bootstrap	Git	GitHub & GitLab	Angular	Google
C#	PHP	.Net	Docker	$\operatorname{SQL}$
Visual Studio Code	Visual Studio 2019	MySQL Server	FileZilla	

### **Education:**

**Purdue University Global** 

4.0 GPA

Associate of Applied Science in Information Technology – Programming and Software Development

March, 2022

# **Experience:**

### **JM Insurance Group**

March 2022- Present

### **Full-stack Developer**

Refreshing the website and converting it from .Net to vanilla HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript. Updating form with accessibility and security in mind and adding a blog section using 11ty and Nunjucks.

#### **KidzBux**

January 2021 – Present

## Front-end developer

From design to implementation, working on the front-end for this app using Figma and Angular.

### **PGIP-Tech**

January 2022 - Present

### **SofDev Mentor**

Guided 14+ interns in various coding experiences, including object-oriented programming issues, React, UI/UX design, accessibility awareness and testing, front-end security awareness and testing, and the importance of "Googling" questions and solutions to coding errors.

## Dev-angela.com

January 2022 – Present

### Owner/Designer/Developer

Designed personal portfolio website, coded in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and jQuery, launched using FileZilla.

### **PGIP-Tech Internship**

10/14/2021 - 12/21/2021

### SofDev Manager

Kept interns on track assigned tasks, worked with Docker, PHP, Git/GitLab and MySQLi on group project, and helped interns pick a path and the stack they needed.

### **Purdue University Global**

July 2020 - March 2022

### **Student**

Learned to write and edit SQL relational databases using MySQL Server, the concepts of object-oriented programming (C#) using VS 2019, how to code, test, and debug HTML, CSS, and JS by hand using Notepad, how to recode non-responsive websites with Flexbox, and how to create a portfolio website.